# Ari (Yu-Sing) Tse

11a Lyon Ave, St Luke's, Auckland 1025 Home Ph: 09-8461878 Mobile Ph: 021-171-2135

Email: aritse23@gmail.com Date of Birth: 23 July 1991

## **Profile**

I am an Auckland University graduate that has a Bachelor of Science Major in Computer Science with specialization in Information Systems. My current goal is to engage in a career that will allow me to make the most out of my skillset while gaining new experience and knowledge. Getting along and working together with peers has always been a strength of mine as I have an easily approachable and outgoing personality, although I also work really well independently. As a kinaesthetic learner, I am able to adapt fast and learn quickly in a working environment, especially through examples and practice.

## **Skills**

# **Computing Skills**

- Basic C# and XML
- Basic HTML and CSS
- Prototyping with Visual Studio LightSwitch
- Prototyping with Microsoft Expression Blend
- Microsoft Office(Word, Excel, Access, Powerpoint)
- General computing knowledge
- Adobe Photoshop, Gimpshop
- Adobe Illustrator, Inkscape (Vectoring)
- Adobe InDesign

## Language

- English
- Cantonese
- Mandarin(minor)

Numeracy and Calculation Skills Leadership Teamwork Communication

## **Education and Qualifications**

- 2013 University of Auckland
  - o Bachelor of Science in Computer Science Major and Information Systems specialisation
- 2009 Mt Roskill Grammar School
  - o NCEA Level 1,2,3

# **Work Experience**

## **ShowBox Consultant Group LTD (2014)**

- Roles: Junior Graphic Designer
  - Worked on a project for New Bruce Lee Sushi shop opening in Auckland City which included redesigning the menu boards for the shop. During this project, I was able to learn the importance of time management and working around a client's requirements. I was also able to improve and increase my knowledge in design software such as Indesign and Photoshop.

# Arzion Plumbing and Gas LTD (2012 - 2014)

- Roles: Casual Labour
  - Working under Arzion Plumbing and Gas Ltd helped vastly mature my problem solving skills as well as making precise calculations and measurements. Good teamwork was also a very important and essential quality required for carrying out the work. During the times I have spent here, I have also witnessed the importance of building relationships with clients and customers.

# Newton Pharmacy Sport & Health K' Rd (2010 – 2012)

- Roles: Pharmacy Sales Assistant, Lotto Retail, Passport Photographer
  - Ouring my time spent at Newton Pharmacy Sport and Health on K' Rd, I have gained experience in operating and managing multiple tills at the same time, honing my ability to perform at an efficient pace. I was given the responsibility to open and close the shop, which includes calculating the "end of day balance report". Having been entrusted with the responsibility of taking passport photos for customers meant that I was in charge of making sure the photos met national requirements and standards. Another important experience I have gained would be working with a very diverse range of customers, which taught me how to deal with difficult situations that may arise.

# "Just Smash It" Badminton Coach at Blockhouse Bay Intermediate (2010 – 2012)

- Roles: Head Coach
  - Since being a coach, I have learnt to become a confident leader and an inspiration to the people that I work with. Throughout this coaching experience I have realised the importance of time-management and keeping students under control as a leader. I always experienced with new creative ideas to make each lesson different and fun for the students while allowing them to learn at a reasonable pace. Sometimes, things do not go as planned which allowed me to familiarise myself with the idea of improvising and problem solving.

# **Extracurricular Activities**

## 2014

- Co-Founder and Designer for street wear label "Decipher."
- Participation in Little Help Project
- Participation in designs on www.designcrowd.co.nz
- Participation in designs on www.threadless.com

## 2013

- Designed quotation and invoice forms for Arzion Plumbing and Gas LTD
- Co-founder and Designer for social network "Idearific" (still in development stages)
- Member of Hong Kong Engineering Students Association
- Participation in designs on www.deviantart.com

## 2012

- Just Smash It Badminton Coach
- Contestant for Footlocker art contest
- Member of Kiwi Asian Club
- Member of Hong Kong Engineering Students Association

# **Voluntary Work Experience**

#### 2010

Just Smash It Badminton Programme Assistant Coach (Mt Roskill Intermediate Term 2)

### 2009

- Auckland International Badminton Tournament Line Judge
- Just Smash It Badminton Programme Assistant Coach (Mt Roskill Grammar Term 4)

#### 2006

- Equinox International Badminton Tournament Line Judge

# **Awards/Achievements**

## 2012

- NZ Badminton "Just Smash It" Coaching Certification

#### 2011

Cisco Curriculum Networking Certification

## 2010

- Just Smash It Assistant Badminton Coach Certification

#### 2009

- Prefect for Mount Roskill Grammar School
- Peer Support Leader for Mount Roskill Grammar School
- Hillary House Captain
- Hillary House Committee
- Mount Roskill Grammar School Award for student coach

#### 2008

- Selected for NZ Badminton's Elite Training Programme
- Hillary House Committee

## 2007

- Selected for Northern NZ Badminton Team 1 June Bevan Cup (Australia vs NZ)
- 1<sup>st</sup> place in Under 17's Australasian June Bevan Team Tournament
- Boys Doubles Winner Australasian Under 17's Badminton Championships
- Mixed Doubles Runner Up Australasian Under 17's Badminton Championships
- Peter Snell Institute of Sport Certificate Award

# **Interests**

Technology, Animations, Games, Design, Architecture, Sports, Aesthetics, Dance, Trends, Puzzles, Magic Tricks, Illusions

# Reference

Arthur Bauld (Newton Pharmacy MANAGER) 021-299-0771
Brandon Wang (ShowBox Consultant Group DIRECTOR) 021-898-873
Cliff Freeman (Just Smash It Program MANAGER) 021-155-7227
Debby Choi (Arzion Plumbing & Gas MANAGER) 021-166-6524